{"questions":[{"question":"kariiiiiiiiiiiin","level":1,"answers":["Y","H","G","F"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":0},{"question":"which of type following is highest degree\n of integration in cloud computing?","level":2,"answers":["Caas","Aaas","Paas","Saas"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":3},{"question":" Is TDD an Agile methodology?","level":1,"answers":["Yes","No","I dont know","we didnt learn about it"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":0},{"question":"hii please woork already","level":1,"answers":["yes maan","OK","fine","what eveeer"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":0},{"question":"this is a test q","level":1,"answers":["h","k","l","4"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":0},{"question":"When does the requirements step gets into the project ?","level":2,"answers":["In the first levels","level after design","before writing the first document","In the development stage"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":1},{"question":"Which of the following is an Agile role?","level":2,"answers":["Product owner","Manager","Secretary","Lab Worker"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":0},{"question":"What is quality analyst in testing?","level":1,"answers":["quality assurance throughout hardware development life cycle","quality assurance and solving bugs ","applies the principles and practices of software quality assurance","testing hardware issues"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":2},{"question":"How many values and principles Agile has?","level":1,"answers":["Two","Three","Four","Five"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":2},{"question":"How do you use QA in Agile?","level":2,"answers":["talk with the manager once in two weeks","Attend daily stand ups","send updates evrey two weeks","in agile we work seperately"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":1},{"question":"Which of the following is one of the\n formal reviews process?","level":1,"answers":["improvise a session with group of members","post review activities","talking with the manager about sessions","gathering results"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":1},{"question":"which of the architecture layer is used as\n front end in cloud computing?","level":2,"answers":["client","cloud","soft","all of the mentioned"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":0},{"question":"which of the architecture layer is used as\n front end in cloud computing?","level":2,"answers":["client","cloud","soft","all of the mentioned"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":0},{"question":"which of the architecture layer is used as\n front end in cloud computing?","level":2,"answers":["client","cloud","soft","all of the mentioned"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":0},{"question":"which of the architecture layer is used as\n front end in cloud computing?","level":3,"answers":["client","cloud","soft","all of the mentioned"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":0}]}